{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"219","name":"American Coney Island, Inc.","address":"115 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Charles J. Keros","licenseNumber":"033843","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.30808,42.29446","geojson":{"id":"219","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.3080806299999,42.29445565]},"properties":{"name":"American Coney Island, Inc.","owner":"Charles J. Keros","address":"115 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"033843","establishmentid":"219","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/29/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4319","name":"Bath Tub Pub","address":"125-29 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5358","name":"Road Dogz","address":"33221 Somerset St","zipcode":"48312"},{"establishmentid":"3552","name":"El Bosque Salon","address":"6705 Lafayette Ave W","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1253","name":"Sacred Heart Major Seminary","address":"2701 W Chicago Ave","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"473","name":"J.P.'s West","address":"22234 W Warren Ave","zipcode":"48239"},{"establishmentid":"4151","name":"Greenfield Union Middle","address":"420 W Seven St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1236","name":"Ann Arbor Trail Magnet School","address":"7635 Chatham St","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"542","name":"3 ELEVEN ULTRA LOUNGE","address":"22100 W Warren Ave","zipcode":"48239"},{"establishmentid":"261","name":"Park-Joy Bar","address":"23220 Joy Rd","zipcode":"48239"},{"establishmentid":"5044","name":"Delectable Goods LLC","address":"12245 Beech Daly Unit #401154","zipcode":"48239"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"48576","inspectionDate":"2019-07-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\r\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\r\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\r\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\r\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\r\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\r\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\r\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\r\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-07-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"SALAD PREP AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-07-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Food","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-07-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-07-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44698","inspectionDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"SALAD STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"6-403.11","violationDescription":"(A) Areas designated for EMPLOYEES to eat, drink, and use tobacco shall be located so that FOOD, EQUIPMENT, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES are protected from contamination.\r\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be located in a designated room or area where contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES can not occur.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/employee storage area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Contaminates","subProblem":"Single use","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate to a designated area that does not contaminate items or surfaces."},{"violationCode":"6-403.11","violationDescription":"(A) Areas designated for EMPLOYEES to eat, drink, and use tobacco shall be located so that FOOD, EQUIPMENT, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES are protected from contamination.\r\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be located in a designated room or area where contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES can not occur.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/employee storage area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Contaminates","subProblem":"Food","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate to a designated area that does not contaminate items or surfaces."},{"violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F thawed or partially thawed","subProblem":"At room temperature","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store under refrigeration."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\r\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\r\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\r\n         (2)     The container; and\r\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Smoking","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Smoke only in designated areas as restricted above."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on face","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide beard net."},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."}]},{"inspectionid":"42461","inspectionDate":"2018-06-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Routine inspections","subItem":"of premises for evidence of pests","problemDescription":"Not performed","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Inspections must be performed as stated above."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40743","inspectionDate":"2017-11-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"violationCode":"6-403.11","violationDescription":"(A) Areas designated for EMPLOYEES to eat, drink, and use tobacco shall be located so that FOOD, EQUIPMENT, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES are protected from contamination.\r\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be located in a designated room or area where contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES can not occur.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/employee storage area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Contaminates","subProblem":"Food","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate to a designated area that does not contaminate items or surfaces."},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"restroom","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."}]},{"inspectionid":"38648","inspectionDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-501.112","violationDescription":"Dead or trapped birds, insects, rodents, and other pests shall be removed from control devices and the PREMISES at a frequency that prevents their accumulation,  decomposition, or the attraction of pests.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dead/trapped pest(s)","subItem":"flies","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."}]},{"inspectionid":"36618","inspectionDate":"2016-09-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-10-31T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"219"}}